<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talk &amp; Chat with Santa Claus</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="disconnected">Turn on dedicated VPN to secure your connection</string>
    <string name="privacy">      By clicking you are Agreeing to  <font fgcolor="#4196F8">Privacy Policy</font>\n                            and <font fgcolor="#4196F8">Terms &amp; Conditions</font></string>
    <string name="privacy_brief"><b>Privacy Policy</b>
\nwe recognize that privacy is significant. This Privacy Policy applies to all apps (Android) under the publisher name of "ITS Digital Era". We have created this Policy to explain our privacy practices so you can understand what information about you is collected, used and disclosed. We collect information from you in order to provide corresponding service and better user experience. With your consent of this Privacy Policy, your usage, statistics, input while using our apps would be collected.
\n\n<b>Special note</b>
\nOur application has nothing to do with the gambling or batting of Tagged, Tagged and Our application is just for live score and cricket information.
\n\n<b>Our Privacy Commitment</b>
\nThis application respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the use of your information is important to us. We do not collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Services to you.
\n\n<b>Permissions in this Application are the Following</b>
\nInternet Permissions
\n\n<b>Changes to this Privacy Policy</b>
\nWe may change this privacy policy from time to time by posting the most current privacy policy and its effective date. If we change this privacy policy substantially, we may bring such changes to your attention by explicit notice on this page.
\n\n<b>Third-party links</b>
\nWe do not include or offer third-party products or services on our applications.
\n\n<b>Children Privacy</b>
\nOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (Children). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
\n\n<b>Contact Us</b>
\nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact our team.
\nYou can find out more information by clicking on the following link:</string>
    <!--    <string name="four">1. I pray that you and your family be surrounded by the Spirit and filled with an overwhelming feeling of happiness and peace in this holiday season. May God bless you and your family more in this holiday season!-->
    <!--\n2. Praying that you celebrate this Christmas season with hearts that are full of hope, love, and faith. Wishing that all the beautiful things be showered unto you this holiday season. May the Lord be with you! Merry Christmas!-->
    <!--\n3. This season has become so special because God has given you the best gift anyone can ever give. Now that we are given the gift of eternal life and salvation, let us continue to do more for the Lord. Happy holidays!-->
    <!--\n4. As you celebrate the Christmas season with your family, be assured that you are all included in my prayers. May the Lord bless you with more prosperous and beautiful years to come.-->
    <!--\n5. Lift your hearts in praise to the Lord and feel him shower you with his kindness and love. Praying that you have a blessed and joyful Christmas celebration this year. God bless you!-->
    <!--\n6. We have always been surrounded by God’s angels. Praying that you be enveloped in these angels’ wings and filled with warmth and bliss this holiday season. Merry Christmas!-->
    <!--\n7. Since God has given us his only son, may we all be worthy and acceptant of his grace. Sending you love and light in this Christmas season.-->
    <!--\n8. Christmas is a time for friends and family, but let us not forget to celebrate the birth of our savior as a family or as friends. Let us be grateful and thankful for the greatest gift we have ever been given.-->
    <!--\n9. Let the Spirit of God fill your home with peace and serenity this holiday season. This will be a great time for you and your family to celebrate with God. Enjoy your holidays!-->
    <!--\n10. I hope you celebrate your Christmas season with a grateful heart. May the Lord shower you with more blessings!-->
    <!--\n11. Christmas is my favorite season because my savior is once again celebrating his birth. Let us celebrate together and enjoy the promises that God has made for us. Enjoy the holidays everyone!-->
    <!--\n12. God has given us a gift that nobody can ever surpass. So as its receiver, we should make sure to receive it with open arms and be thankful at all times. May the love of the Lord envelope us with warmth, peace, and joy this holiday season.</string>-->
    <!--    -->
    <!--    -->
    <!--    <string name="three">Santa Claus, also known as Father Christmas, Saint Nicholas, Saint Nick, Kris Kringle, or simply Santa, is a legendary character originating in Western Christian culture who is said to bring children gifts on Christmas Eve of toys and candy or coal or nothing, depending on whether they are "naughty-or-nice". He supposedly accomplishes this with the aid of Christmas elves, who make the toys in his workshop, often said to be at the North Pole, and flying reindeer who pull his sleigh through the air.-->
    <!--\nThe modern character of Santa is based on folklore traditions surrounding Saint Nicholas, the English figure of Father Christmas and the Dutch figure of Sinterklaas.-->
    <!--\nSanta is generally depicted as a portly, jolly, white-bearded man, often with spectacles, wearing a red coat with white fur collar and cuffs, white-fur-cuffed red trousers, red hat with white fur, and black leather belt and boots, carrying a bag full of gifts for children. He is commonly portrayed as laughing in a way that sounds like "ho-ho-ho". This image became popular in the United States and Canada in the 19th century due to the significant influence of the 1823 poem "A Visit from St. Nicholas". Caricaturist and political cartoonist Thomas Nast also played a role in the creation of Santa's image. This image has been maintained and reinforced through song, radio, television, children\'s books, family Christmas traditions, films, and advertising.</string>-->


    <string name="one">1. Quiet on the night before Christmas. Magic is coming into the world. A fairy tale is walking home in dreams looking to us. May the Nativity of Christ give your heart joy and peace, and hope shine on your family with a Christmas star.
\n2. Faith is a miracle that will awaken love and kindness! Merry Christmas. We wish you happiness, joy, peace, light, warmth. May all your dreams come true!
\n3. May the Lord help you in your efforts, love, and understanding. Jesus Christ was born into a world where evil and sin. The holy God descended from heaven to save everyone. Let the holy angels circle over your house, sparkling with the golden lights.
\n4. This Christmas, I wish everyone happiness, love, kindness. May the birth of Christ will bring you peace and joy.
\n5. Faith will power you. May the Lord help you with everything! On this bright winter evening, May health is stronger, and goodness comes into the house every minute. Merry Christmas!
\n6. Birth of Christ is that fabulous holiday in which all dreams and wishes come true. That’s why I wish you only good health and luck. Let the sun not leave your home and your heart. Merry Christmas!
\n7. On this beautiful Christmas, let love fill the heart, and all pain will go away. Let the ray of goodness look through your window in the morning. May tomorrow be more beautiful than yesterday with God’s blessing!
\n8. Let miracles continue, and joy burn in your eyes. On the enjoyable Christian holiday, the day of Christmas, Let the Guiding Star shine brightly in the sky! May the angels of the Lord protect you from all troubles!
\n9. Best wishes to my beloved friend for the fantastic year ahead! May the happiness always shine above you and love to surround you! Merry Christmas!
\n10. Every new year comes big challenges and obstacles in life. I wish you courage, hope, and faith to overcome all the hurdles you face. May you have a great year and a wonderful time ahead! Merry Christmas &amp; Happy New Year!
\n11. On this cozy Christmas holiday, I wish you happiness into the house so that the whole family is healthy and all dreams come true! Do not let your soul get tired of doing good. I wish you to live in peace and joy!
\n12. A star shines in the sky. It’s Christmas. I wish you on this beautiful evening happiness, peace, prosperity to you. Let your wishes come true. Merry Christmas! Let the bright holiday bring you faith, goodness, love, good luck, health, and happiness.
\n13. In the beauty of the season and the joy of Christmas Day, May you find the true meaning that brings you happiness. As I think about our friendship and how happy it has made me, I want to wish you happiness in the year to come!
\n14. Keep your spiritual purity and faith in God. May this magical day make your dreams come true! I wish you happiness and luck. May the angel protect you from sorrows and difficulties. Merry Christmas &amp; happy new year!
\n15. Please accept my honest thanks and best wishes for the holiday season and the upcoming new year! Thank you for allowing me to work with you this year. It has been an honor and a precious experience for me. I wish you a merry Christmas and a new year filled with all good things.
\n16. Let Baby christ guide you on the way to add health to you. Let flowers bloom in your soul. May there be simple joys, and inspire again and again with hope, faith, and love to your life.
\n17. Merry Christmas. On this bright holiday, I want to wish you can see only the good in the world around you and find everything good in people making all your dreams come true. Sincerely believe and never forget about pure human happiness. I wish you to appreciate everything that you have and enjoy every moment of your life
\n18. Where evil spells are powerless, good always wins. Let the angel protect your beautiful home. May this enjoyable holiday will warm your hearts. I wish you a Merry Christmas! On this day, Christ was born.
\n19. On the day of this bright Christmas of Christ, say only kind words. Let your head spin happily from this holy celebration.
\n20. A bright star is lighting in the sky, which brings hope to all of us. So let it always shine for you as it never leaves you. May your house full of happiness, and everything is perfect as always. Merry Christmas to you! Love you!</string>
    <string name="two">Christmas is an annual festival commemorating the birth of Jesus Christ, observed primarily on December 25 as a religious and cultural celebration among billions of people around the world. A feast central to the Christian liturgical year, it is preceded by the season of Advent or the Nativity Fast and initiates the season of Christmastide, which historically in the West lasts twelve days and culminates on Twelfth Night. Christmas Day is a public holiday in many countries, is celebrated religiously by a majority of Christians, as well as culturally by many non-Christians, and forms an integral part of the holiday season organized around it.

\nThe traditional Christmas narrative recounted in the New Testament, known as the Nativity of Jesus, says that Jesus was born in Bethlehem, in accordance with messianic prophecies. When Joseph and Mary arrived in the city, the inn had no room and so they were offered a stable where the Christ Child was soon born, with angels proclaiming this news to shepherds who then spread the word.

\nThere are different hypotheses regarding the date of Jesus birth and in the early fourth century, the church fixed the date as December 25. This corresponds to the traditional date of the winter solstice on the Roman calendar. It is exactly nine months after Annunciation on March 25, also the date of the spring equinox. Most Christians celebrate on December 25 in the Gregorian calendar, which has been adopted almost universally in the civil calendars used in countries throughout the world. However, part of the Eastern Christian Churches celebrate Christmas on December 25 of the older Julian calendar, which currently corresponds to January 7 in the Gregorian calendar. For Christians, believing that God came into the world in the form of man to atone for the sins of humanity, rather than knowing Jesus\' exact birth date, is considered to be the primary purpose in celebrating Christmas.</string>
</resources>